The Last Time is a drama, romance film directed by Michael Caleo.
Ted Ryker is the top salesman in the New York office of a business machine company; the corporate stock lives
by quarterly sales numbers, the competition is keen, and the economy may be in a downturn.
Ted's company is marking time until a new product is
ready – probably in a few months.
Into the mix comes a new hire, a callow Midwesterner named
Jamie, who's come East with his fiancée Belisa.
Ted, played by Michael Keaton.
Jamie Bashant, played by Brendan Fraser.
John, played by Daniel Stern.
Belisa, played by Amber Valletta.
Arthur, played by Richard Kuhlman.
Alvarez, played by Alexis Cruz.
Last Holiday is a 2006 American romantic comedy-drama film directed by
Wayne Wang and written by Jeffrey Price and Peter S.
The film is loosely based on the 1950 British film of the same name by J.
The film stars Queen Latifah as Georgia Byrd, a humble department store assistant who is
told that she has a rare brain condition and only has a few weeks to live.
She promptly decides to spend her remaining funds on a
luxury holiday in Europe before she dies.
Price and Seaman wanted John Candy for the main role but, after Candy's
death, Latifah's agent suggested a new version starring her.
Produced by Robert Zemeckis' ImageMovers, the film was
released by Paramount Pictures on January 13, 2006.
The film underperformed at the box office, having grossed $43.3 million against a budget of $45 million and received
mixed reviews from critics, though Latifah's performance was universally praised for her charm and humor.
The tone is emotional.